import 'package:poly2/exam_model.dart';

class QuestionsData {
  static List<Question> questions = [
    Question(
      questionText: "Hello",
      options: ["Elma", "Kitap", "Kalem", "Merhaba"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Dog",
      options: ["Ev", "Köpek", "Telefon", "Kalem"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Book",
      options: ["Öğretmen", "Çanta", "Kitap", "Su"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "House",
      options: ["Ev", "Araba", "Bardak", "Çocuk"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Job",
      options: ["Kalem", "İş", "Merhaba", "Köpek"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Garden",
      options: ["Çalışma", "Deniz", "Bahçe", "Kitap"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Always",
      options: ["Hiçbir şey", "Her zaman", "Ev", "Şehir"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Quickly",
      options: ["Çanta", "Kitap", "Yavaş", "Hızlıca"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Decision",
      options: ["Yardım", "Çocuk", "Karar", "Yatak"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Friendly",
      options: ["Düşman", "Arkadaş canlısı", "Yabancı", "İş"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Experience",
      options: ["Kişilik", "Oyun", "Deneyim", "Zaman"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Journey",
      options: ["Yer", "Yolculuk", "Hedef", "Okul"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Ambition",
      options: ["Güven", "Cümle", "Hırs", "Öğretmen"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Achievement",
      options: ["Şaka", "Başarı", "Bilgi", "Zorluk"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Predict",
      options: ["Yazmak", "Kaydetmek", "Tahmin etmek", "İzlemek"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Convince",
      options: ["Düzenlemek", "İkna etmek", "Buluşmak", "Şüphelenmek"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Comprehensive",
      options: ["Sınırlı", "Kapsamlı", "Basit", "Yalnızca"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Distinguish",
      options: ["İncelemek", "Karıştırmak", "Ayırt etmek", "Uzak durmak"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Insight",
      options: ["Yalan", "Oyun", "İçgörü", "Çalışma"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    Question(
      questionText: "Significance",
      options: ["Hafiflik", "Önem", "Boşluk", "Tarz"],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
  ];
}

